

CV Md Tanvir Hossain Contact No: +88 01313922323 E-mail: wasib.cse@gmail.com

About Me

I am a person who is positive about every aspect of life. I am punctual and responsible. There are many things I like to do, to see, and to experience. I like to read, to write, to think, to dream, and to smell the wind coming from the ocean.

Interest

- Coding
- Swimming
- ***** Travelling,
- Photography.

Career Objective

It's my dream to establish myself as an efficient and innovative executive in any suitable position. I would like to show my immense aspiration to become a quick learner and to prove myself as a sincere and energetic person through extensive hard working and integrity.

Language Skills

- Fluent in reading,
- Mid-level writing, and speaking both in English and Bengali.

Education

▶ B.sc of Computer Science Engineer (B.S.C.)

Major: Computer Science Year: 2021

Institution: Southern University Bangladesh.

▶ Higher Secondary Certificate (H.S.C.) [Science]

Year: 2012

Institution: J. M. C. C College,

Chittagong Board.

➤ Secondary School Certificate(S.S.C.) [Science]

Year: 2009

Institution: Chittagong Port Authority High School,

Chittagong Board.

EXPERIENCE

- ➤ 2018-2019 Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Lead finder Orbeen
- 2019-2021 Graphics Design Fiveer.com Upwork.com
- ➤ 2013-2018 Web design & Development Fiveer.com Upwork.com Freelancer.com

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

- An Efficient Energy & Cost Saving Electricity Production System
- My project claims very effective and productive alternative to produce energy not only in Bangladesh but also for the rest of the world
- > It works very easily to produce electricity
- The chosen microcontroller for this project is microchip PIC 16f73,diod, crystalloid IR receiver, mosfet

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Installing and configuring computer, hardware software , network's systems ,printers and scanners
- Providing technical support across the company
- Setting up accounts for new users
- Testing new technology
- Possibly training junior staf

Training Program

- Microsoft Office Program (Advanced excel, Word, Pawer Point Presentation)
- Web developer programing hero
- Graphics design
- Search engine optimization (SEO)

Extra-Curricular Activities:

- ➤ Voluntarily organized and accomplished philanthropic activities with friends under the banner named "Unity for Humanity".
- Actively participated in local sports competitions

Skills

- > Skill on advanced Microsoft Excel.
- Microsoft Word, Microsoft Power Point & Visio.
- Full stack web developer
- > Graphics designer
- ➤ Mail commination (Microsoft Outlook)
- ➤ Well Knowledge about javascript
- > Inherent can-do attitude and obedient

Willingness to take responsibilities and challenges

Personal Information

❖ Name: Md Tanvir Hossain .❖ Father's name: Md Delwar Hossain❖ Mother's name: Rokeya Begum

❖ Present address : Holding No-1197, Holding Name- dweep mansion, 4th floor

(Right), Boropol, Halishohor, Chittagong.

❖ Permanent address : Vill/P.O- Islampur, P.S- Begumgani, Dist- Noakhali.

❖ Date of birth: 17/09/1994❖ Sex:Male❖ Religion: Islam❖ Marital status: Unmarried.

❖ Nationality : Bangladeshi (by born)

❖ National ID No. : 4656147081

❖ Blood Group : O+
 ❖ Hight : 5.10"

Reference: 1

Name : Md. Hasan

Designation: vice president & head of

branch

Institution : United commercial bank

Contact No : 01711809731 E-mail : hasan.md@ucb.com.bd

Reference: 2

Name : Md omar faruk Designation : headmaster

Institution: cufl

Contact No : 01790800605 E-mail : faruk.cufl@gmail.com

These are only a few of my accomplishments. I look forward to speaking with you in more detail about my record. Here I put all my information's which are based on reliability and authenticity.

Signature: Md Tanvir Hossain